{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Unpaired H-bond donors and acceptors are found in the hydrophobic core of a protein", "opta": "only at the ends of a-helices", "optb": "only at the turns connecting p-strands", "optc": "only on Pro residues", "optd": "rarely", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For the unfolding reaction of Protein G, \u0394H\u00b0 =210.6 kJ/mol, this means that", "opta": "unfolding is favored enthalpically", "optb": "folding is favored enthalpically", "optc": "the entropy is positive at all temperatures", "optd": "the entropy is negative at all temperatures", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Attractive Vander Waals forces occur between", "opta": "apolar molecules in the liquid state", "optb": "any pair of nearby atoms", "optc": "polar molecules in the solid state", "optd": "only if other forces are less favorable", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following forces is the most favorable for protein folding?", "opta": "Conformational entropy", "optb": "Hydrophobic Interactions", "optc": "Vander Waals interactions", "optd": "Hydrogen bonds", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "At the midpoint of a temperature transition curve,", "opta": "half of the protein is denatured", "optb": "Keq = 1.0 and \u0394G = 0", "optc": "[Native] = [Unfolded]", "optd": "All of these", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is the most correct?", "opta": "Charged amino acids are never buried in the interior of a protein", "optb": "Charged amino acids are seldom buried in the interior of a protein", "optc": "All hydrophobic amino acids are buried when a protein folds", "optd": "Tyrosine is only found in the interior of proteins", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following forces is the most unfavorable for protein folding?", "opta": "Conformational entropy", "optb": "Hydrophobic interactions", "optc": "Vander Waals interactions", "optd": "Electrostatic interactions", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Since \u0394G\u00b0 = -RTlnK", "opta": "a 10-fold increase in K decreases \u0394G\u00b0 by about 10-fold", "optb": "a 10-fold decrease in K decreases \u0394G\u00b0 by about 2.3*RT", "optc": "a 10-fold increase in K decreases \u0394G\u00b0 by about 2.3*RT", "optd": "a 10-fold decrease in K increases \u0394G\u00b0 by about 10-fold", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The correlation between free energy \u0394G transfer between the aqueous/organic phases and the surface area of amino acid residues", "opta": "reflects the reduction in solvent-accessible area during protein folding", "optb": "is only meaningful for the polar amino acids", "optc": "ignores the important contribution of the peptide bond", "optd": "is similar to effects seen with SDS denaturation", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the egg white protein, ovalbumin, is denatured in a hard-boiled egg, then which of the following is least affected?", "opta": "The primary structure of ovalbumin", "optb": "The secondary structure of ovalbumin", "optc": "The tertiary structure of ovalbumin", "optd": "The quaternary structure of ovalbumin", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Buried hydrophobic side chains in a globular protein fit into a hole formed by the side chains of", "opta": "1-3 other amino acids", "optb": "5-7 other amino acids", "optc": "9-12 other amino acids", "optd": "13-15 other amino acids", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}